justyap.com 2019-07-31

# JUSTYAP

Effective date : November 1, 2015

## Who We Are and What This Policy Is

We at Reach communications Inc("Reach" or "JustYap", “Us”, “We, or “Our”) know You (“You” or “Your”) care about how Your personal information (“Personal Information”) is used and shared, and we take Your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.

By using or accessing the “JustYap” mobile application (“App”) or the website located at [www.JustYap.com](http://www.justyap.com/) (the “Website”) (collectively, the “Service”) in any manner, You acknowledge that You accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and You hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share Your information in the following ways.

To be clear, by “Personal Information” we mean information about You that is personally identifiable, like Your name, physical address, email address, billing information (such as Your credit card number) and phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with this information. Remember that Your use of Service is at all times subject to the Terms of Use, which incorporates this Privacy Policy. 

## Do You Live In the European Union? 

IF YOU ARE A USER ACCESSING THE SERVICE OR WEBSITE FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, ASIA, OR ANY OTHER REGION WITH LAWS OR REGULATIONS GOVERNING PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE THAT DIFFER FROM UNITED STATES LAWS, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SERVICE OR WEBSITE, WHICH ARE GOVERNED BY UNITED STATES LAW, THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND OUR END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT, YOU MAY BE TRANSMITTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION IN YOUR COUNTRY AND YOU HEREBY CONSENT TO SUCH TRANSMISSION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.

## Here’s the Info We Collect

JustYap collects only the following types of information:

### Information You Provide to Us:

We receive and store any information You knowingly provide to Us. For example, through the registration process and/or through Your account settings, we may collect Personal Information such as Your name, phone number, email address and photo).

In addition, You will also be asked to provide access to Your phone number and allow Us to access Your mobile device’s address book. A copy of the names and phone number in Your address book will be stored on our servers and only used to provide the Service to You (such as: notifying You when Your contacts become active on the App, let You know which of Your contacts is already a Service users, correctly display Your contact names to You, etc.).

Also, if You provide Your third-party account credentials (such as Your Facebook log-in info) to us or otherwise sign in to the Service through a third party site or service, You understand some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into Your account with, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to the Service is covered by this Privacy Policy. 

### Sharing with the JustYap Community or Social Media: 

The Service may permit You to publish or post Your Content – to the JustYap community (or on social media such as Facebook or Twitter). If You elect to share such information – it will be disclosed to Your intended audience. The functionality of the App will make it clear when You are about to share information in this manner – and the audience it will be disclosed to.

### Your JustYap Number:

Since Service users may add Your special Service phone number to their address book and see that You are registered with the Service – we do not consider Your JustYap number private information. 

### Your Audio Calls:

Let’s be very clear – WE DO NOT RECORD YOUR CALLS. That would be creepy! Sometimes call are transmitted by Our servers and, in such case, they will be stored briefly in volatile memory (RAM) solely to enable transmission (and we cannot listen to such calls).

### Call Record:

We also maintain a Call Detail Record (CDR - see http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Call_detail_record) for each message and call that goes through the Service. These are industry standard records used by all phone companies. We maintain this information in order to better understand network behavior and trends (numbers of messages and calls made by users, typical destinations, call lengths, network type, etc.), detect potential outages and technical issues (this helps us notice things like a drop in call volume in a certain geography, a shift in call length, a change in typical networks, etc.) and for public safety reasons. All log analysis is done in an anonymous, aggregate, non-personally identifiable manner. We may look into a specific Call Detail Record in response to a customer support request. We maintain CDRs for a period of no more than 30 months.

### Your Location:

To the extent You enable it within the App – we will collect Your locate information. We will not use such information for any purpose except when requested by You.

### Other Information Collected from Your Use of the Website or App (Like “Cookies”):

Whenever You interact with the Website or App, We may automatically receive and record information on Our server logs from Your browser or device, which may include Your IP address, device identification, “cookie” information, the type of browser and/or device You’re using to access Our Service, and the page or feature You requested. “Cookies” are identifiers We transfer to Your browser or device that allow Us to recognize Your browser or device and tell Us how and when pages and features in Our Website or Site or App are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on Your browser or device to prevent or limit Your device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent You from taking advantage of some of our features.

Our advertising partners may also transmit cookies to Your browser or device, when You click on ads that appear on the Service. Also, if You click on a link to a third party website or service, such third party may also transmit cookies to You. Again, this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties, and We aren’t responsible for their privacy policies and practices.

We may use this data to customize content for You that we think You might like, based on Your usage patterns. We may also use it to improve the Service – for example, this data can tell us how often users use a particular feature of the Service, and we can use that knowledge to make the Service interesting to as many users as possible. 

### Information Collected From Other Websites and Do Not Track Policy:

Through cookies we place on Your browser or device, we may collect information about Your online activity after You leave our Services. Just like any other usage information we collect, this information allows us to improve the Services and customize Your online experience, and otherwise as described in this Privacy Policy. Your browser may offer You a “Do Not Track” option, which allows You to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that You do not wish such operators to track certain of Your online activities over time and/or across different websites. Our Services do not support Do Not Track requests at this time, which means that we collect information about Your online activity both while You are using the Services and after You leave our Services.

## Here’s How We Use Your Info

JustYap uses Your Personal Information as follows:

  * To provide You with the features, functions and benefits of the Service.
  * To help us internally operate and maintain the Service (such as, for the purposes of fixing malfunctions, testing our security systems, etc.).
  * To enhance, improve and further develop the Service (such as, creating new features or functions, refining the user experience, increasing the technical performance of our Products, etc.).
  * We will use Your contact information to provide You with notices relate to Your use of the Service (such as account notifications and legal notices). 
  * We will use Your contact information (such as, Your email address) to provide You with promotional and marketing emails. You can opt-out of receiving certain types of promotional and marketing emails – but in such case You may not receive the full benefit of the Service. Opting-out can be done by following the instructions set forth in the email (usually near the bottom).
  * To help personalize the Service experience for You (such as, remembering Your information so You will not have to enter it each time You open the App on Your mobile device).
  * And for the other purposes referenced in the “Who We Share Info With” section below.

## Info that Does Not Identify You.

We may anonymize the information we collect from You so that You are not individually identified, and provide that information to our partners or the public in general. For example, we may publish public reports regarding how often calls are made to various countries. To be clear – such disclosures will not identify You!

## Who We Share Info With.

We neither rent nor sell Your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We may share Your Personal Information with some third parties – but only as described in this section:

### With Your Consent:

We may share You’re Your Content with third parties with Your consent. The functionality of the Website and App will make it clear when You are about to share information in this manner – and the audience it will be disclosed to.

### Agents (Such as, Our Payment Processor):

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share Your information with them to provide products or services to You. For example, we may use third parties to process payments, You SMS messages (such as for Service authentication), provide marketing communications, infrastructure and IT services, provide customer service, process and administer consumer surveys, etc.

In the course of providing such services, these third party providers may have access to Your information. But, they are only authorized to use or disclose Your information in connection with providing us with their services. 

### Profile Information:

If You upload Your name and/or photo to the Service – it will be viewable by other Service users who have Your number or with whom You participate in a Service group (community).

### Online Status:

We will share Your online status with other Service users.

### Business Transfers:

We may choose to buy or sell the assets of Reach communications Inc. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Your information could be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.

### Protection of JustYap and Others:

We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our Terms of Use; detect and handle payment fraud, or otherwise to protect the rights, property, or safety of Justyap, our employees, our users, or others.

### California Residents:

UNDER CALIFORNIA CIVIL CODE SECTIONS 1798.83-1798.84, CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS ARE ENTITLED TO ASK US FOR A NOTICE IDENTIFYING THE CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WHICH WE SHARE WITH OUR AFFILIATES AND/OR THIRD PARTIES FOR MARKETING PURPOSES, AND PROVIDING CONTACT INFORMATION FOR SUCH AFFILIATES AND/OR THIRD PARTIES. IF YOU ARE A CALIFORNIA RESIDENT AND WOULD LIKE A COPY OF THIS NOTICE, PLEASE SUBMIT A WRITTEN REQUEST TO: [support@justyap.com](mailto:support@justyap.com) OR Reach communications Inc. (ATTN: Privacy), 99 Almaden Boulevard, Suite 600, San Jose, CA 95113.

## What You can Do to Your Personal Information.

### Deleting Your account:

You can delete Your account by emailing customer support at [support@justyap.com](mailto:support@justyap.com) In addition, You can simply go to the “More” tab in the App and tap the “Deactivate Account” option. Subject to the “Limitations on Deletion” section below, when You request us to delete Your account for the Service, Your data will be permanently deleted from Our servers and access to Your account will be disabled.

### Limitations on Deletion:

Even after You remove information from Your profile or delete Your account, Your Personal Information may be retained by Us on back-up servers indefinitely (excepting Your address book (names an photos) – they will be completely deleted as described in the “Information You Provide to Us” section above.

We will continue to retain and use anonymized data (meaning data that does not specifically identify You). We keep such servers to help protect the stability and availability of the Service (such as protecting it from viruses and malfunctions).

In addition, copies of Your information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been publicly published by Your or otherwise shared by You with others (such as, message You posted to friends on the Service).

We may also retain certain information to prevent identity theft and other misconduct even if deletion has been requested.

We may also indefinitely retain and use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating Your Personal Information after You update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify You 

### Laws and Regulations:

We may also retain Your Personal Information to the extent required to comply with (or we deem it reasonable in light of) any laws or regulations.

## Some Special Google-Related Terms.

We use Google Analytics to help Us anonymously track and report user/visitor behavior information and users' standard log information to the Website and App. This information (including but not limited to: IP address, data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and information processing) helps Us analyze and evaluate how the Website and App are used as part of Our ongoing efforts to improve the Website’s and App's features and services. No personally identifying data is included in this type of reporting. Google Analytics may have access to Your information only for the purposes of performing these tasks and on behalf of Us and under obligation similar in those in this Privacy Policy. For more information about the terms that govern Google Analytics, please visit the Google Analytics terms of service.

We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personal Information of visitors or users. Google will not associate Your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither We nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a device user. We will not associate any data gathered from the Website or App with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless You explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on Our website.

If You do not want Your information to be part of this statistical information gathering, You can disable Google Analytics using the application settings; visit the 'More' screen, tap settings, then disable Google Analytics Collect Data option.

## Opting-Out of Our Emails.

If You don’t want to receive email communications from us such as offers, updated and newsletters – You may simply opt-out of receiving such communications by following the instructions included in each such email (usually a link near the bottom of the email).

## The Location of Your Info.

While Your Personal Information is in our possession, it will be stored at hosting facilities located in the USA. These facilities are either operated by JustYap or our third party providers. By using the Service You are consenting to have Your Personal Information stored, transferred and processed in the USA.

## The Security of Your Info.

JustYap takes certain precautions to protect Your Personal Information and to limit the risk that it will be accessed without authorization, including use of certain industry standard technologies and practices. That said, we cannot guarantee the security of such information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. No security system is perfect - so Your use of the Service is at Your own risk.

If we learn of a security systems bJustyap, then we may attempt to notify You via email, phone, physical mail, or by a posting on Your Service account page - so that You can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Service You consent to receive such notice by electronic means (provided that such consent is void where prohibited by applicable law). To receive a free written notice of a security b Justyap, or if You have any questions about the security of the Service, please contact us at [support@justyap.com](mailto:support@justyap.com)

In addition to the security measures referenced above, Your Service account is protected by a password for Your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to Your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting Your password appropriately and limiting access to Your computer or device and browser by signing off after You 

## Protecting Children.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If You are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Service or send any personal information about Yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If You believe that a child under 13 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at [support@justyap.com](mailto:support@justyap.com)

## Changes to This Policy

This Privacy Policy was last changed on the date set forth at the top of the policy. We’re constantly trying to improve the Service, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time as well, but we will alert You to changes by placing a notice on the [www.JustYap.com](http://www.justyap.com/), by sending You an email, or providing a notification through Your Service account. In addition, We will also edit the date at the top of this policy to reflect the date of the changes. If You use the Service after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been posted, You agree to all of the changes. Use of information We collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.

## Contacting Us.

If You have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to [support@justyap.com](mailto:support@justyap.com) or Reach communications Inc. (ATTN: Privacy), 99 Almaden Boulevard, Suite 600, San Jose, CA 95113.
